onelovenet.com 2018-08-31

# Privacy Policy - Find Singles Free Dating Site OneLoveNet.com, Online Dating Service, Personal Ads

|  Home  

 **Welcome,**

 **login here:**[Free Registration](http://www.onelovenet.com/index.cgi/def/step1/)  
Search Profiles  
What's New?  
My Messages  
Find Singles for Free @ OneLoveNet.com, 100% Free Dating Site & Marchmaking Service. Soon, we will list other 100% free dating sites for you. Stay connected!  
Being a quickly growing free online dating personals website and service, OneLoveNet.com provides new personal ads every day for men, women, boys & girls.|  | 

* * *

Privacy Policy

Last Update: 2018-05-24

**REGISTRATION**  
If you register on OneLoveNet.com as a member, we collect and store all the information you enter. Our Statistics, are derived from these information. This information may be used to target our registered members for new services and promotions. Your e-mail address may be used by OneLoveNet.com and certain partners to contact you regarding new services and products in which you may be interested.  
We also display certain information you enter on your specific profile detail page including but not limited to: your your nick name and some other personal details.

**REGISTRATION OBLIGATIONS**  
If you register in OneLoveNet.com, you agree to:  
(a) provide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself  
(b) maintain and promptly update the Registration Content to keep it true, accurate, current and complete. If you provide any information that is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete, OneLoveNet.com has reasonable grounds to suspect that such information is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete and OneLoveNet.com reserves the right to suspend or terminate your member service.  
Your OneLoveNet.com Account Information and Member Profile are password-protected so that other OneLoveNet.com members and / or third parties will not have the ability to access, edit or delete this personal information. Any password protection system may be vulnerable to certain attacks, and therefore OneLoveNet.com cannot 100% guarantee the protection of your personal information from malicious third parties. We recommend you to do not disclose your password to anyone and change your password from time to time.

**PUBLISHING INFORMATION**  
All of your Publishing Information will be publicly available on OneLoveNet.com and therefore accessible by visitors and members.  
Any Publishing Information that you use on OneLoveNet.com forms becomes public information and you respond for them (including but not limited to the rights of confidentiality and copyrights).  
If you submit any information to OneLoveNet.com to be published on our site through the publishing forms you are deemed to have given consent to the publication of such information.

We will never share your email address or phone numbers with other members, only you can do this by giving away this information on areas where free text can be entered such as profile details or messages between members. We might provide your IP address only to members you contact, just to be able to keep and maintain a high quality site by trying to eliminate scam and fraud as much as possible.

**COOKIES**  
OneLoveNet.com does store some information in "cookies" on your computer. If you use a section of our website that requires a login, your login information may be stored in a cookie for the duration of your browser session. If you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties. This site or the advertisers on this site may use cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process.  
If you want to block the use and saving of cookies from the Site on to their computers hard drive, you should take the necessary steps within your web browser’s settings to block all cookies from the Site. Please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, certain parts of our Site may not function correctly. For information on how to disable cookies, refer to your browser’s documentation.

**YOUR PERSONAL DATA WE COLLECT AND USE**  
We may process your registration data ("registration data"). Registration data may include your email address and eventually your username. The source of this data is you. Registration data is required in order for you to be able to use the service. The legal bases for this processing are consent and the performance of a contract between you and us and/or taking steps, at your request, to enter into such a contract.

We may process your account data ("profile data"). Profile data may include your full name, email address, country, city, address, phone number and personal profile. The source of this data is you. The profile data may be processed for the purposes of providing our services, communicating with you and allowing other members to contact you and get in touch with you. Certain profile data (Age, Ethnicity, Height, Body Type, Hair color, Eye Color, Smoke, Drink, Profession, Education, Children, Marital Status, Religion, Photos you upload) is disclosed publicly on our website. The legal bases for this processing are  
\- consent  
\- our legitimate interests, namely the operation of our business model.

We store your information primarily within our servers located in the USA and the European Economic Area. However, some features and requirements of our service, may involve transferring your information to third-party service providers outside the European Economic Area. When we do similar transfers, the transfers will be covered by the standard data protection clauses adopted by the European Commission or by another appropriate safeguard mechanism such as the Privacy Shield Framework.

**RETAINING AND DELETING PERSONAL DATA**

We will retain your Personal Data for as long as long as you maintain an account or subscription agreement or as otherwise necessary to provide you the Services. We will also retain your Personal Data as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.  
Users may request the deletion of their account by logging into their account or contacting us.  
We will retain and delete your personal data as follows:

We will delete all personal data 30 days after the approval of your account deletion request.  
Your communication data with other members will be deleted 5 years after you delete your account.

Notwithstanding the other provisions, we may retain your personal data where such retention is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person.

**LOG DATA**

When you use the Services, our servers may automatically collect and store information, including information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. This log data may include, but is not limited to, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, the address of the web page you visited before using the Services, the operating system you are using, the date and time of your accessing the Services, geolocation information, type of device, cookie data, and browser signatures.

Use of the Site and Services signifies consent to our use of cookies, including and without limitation Third Party cookies that we may choose to use for analytics or other purposes. You agree that should you disable cookies on your browser, certain aspects of the Services may be unavailable to you, and that we are not responsible for any adverse effects arising from your browser or other computer or mobile settings.

You agree that you are responsible for adhering to all laws, policies, and other regulations in your relevant jurisdiction(s), including but not limited to all laws requiring that cookie use must be disclosed. We disclaim all liability in this area.

**INFORMATION DISCLOSURE**  
OneLoveNet.com does not disclose the collected information (except the Publishing Information) to any third parties, unless acting under the belief that such action is necessary to:  
(a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process  
(b) protect and defend the rights or property of OneLoveNet.com  
(c) act to protect the interests of its members or others.  
We reserve the right to disclose any collected information to authorities where we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be infringing or threatening to infringe, or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with, the title, rights, interests or property of OneLoveNet.com, our members, customers, partners, other web site users or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities.  
We reserve the right to disclose any collected information in response to a judicial order or when we believe that such disclosure is required by law, regulation or administrative order of any court, governmental or regulatory authority.

OneLoveNet.com considers and respects an individual's privacy seriously and importantly. The services we provide require that we collect, process, use, display and distribute certain details you provide us. Therefore, OneLoveNet.com does not guarantee that your information will be protected from exposure in any particular party or group. If you would like to remove your member account you can do this while you are logged in or by contacting us through our contact forms.

We welcome your additional input regarding our Privacy Policy or our services provided to you.  
The data controller responsible for your personal data for is Premier World SRL, a Romania limited liability company; Satu Mare, Romania. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, your rights and/or our data collection practices, please contact our customer support. 

|
